welcome to this session on next level
欢迎参加下届会议
spring boot tooling it's going to be a
spring boot 工具，这将是一个
60 minute session and I'm Andy Clement
60分钟的课程，我是Andy Clement
and this is Chris and Martin and
这是克里斯和马丁，
together we work on the SDS team in
我们一起在SDS团队中工作
Vancouver and Germany just the usual
温哥华和德国平常
statement most of the stuff we're going
陈述我们要去的大部分东西
to show us be in their current release
向我们展示当前版本
but we might show you some stuff preview
但我们可能会向您展示一些内容预览
stuff and when we eventually ship it it
东西，当我们最终发货时
may not look like you see it today so
可能看起来不像您今天看到的那样
just a warning on that you probably know
只是警告您可能知道
what STS is but it just in case you
什么是STS，但以防万一
don't STS is a we take the Eclipse
不要STS是我们拿的Eclipse
distribution put out by Eclipse a few
Eclipse推出的一些发行版
times a year we add in some extra
一年几次，我们增加了一些额外的费用
plugins that make it very easy to work
使工作变得非常容易的插件
with spring and cloud foundry as you'll
随着春天和云铸造厂，你会
see a bit later on today and we wrap
今天晚些时候见，我们包装
that up in something called the spring
在所谓的春天
tool suite distribution if you go to
工具套件分发（如果您要转到
that URL you can grab the latest version
您可以获取最新版本的URL
we put out any 381 release yesterday
我们昨天发布了381版本
that you can grab that's based on the
你可以抓住的是基于
Eclipse neon release that came out in
出现的Eclipse Neon版本
the summertime so whenever there's an
夏天，所以每当有一个
eclipse release or service refresh we
日食发布或服务刷新
follow it in a matter of days with an
在几天之内跟随它
sts package with everything in what are
sts软件包，其中包含所有内容
the plugins that you do in the old days
您过去的插件
they let you do the xml stuff for spring
他们让您在春季做xml的工作
but as we've gone on we've kept up with
但是随着我们的前进，我们跟上了
the times we annotation related stuff
我们注释相关内容的时间
and now we get into the spring boot
现在我们进入 spring boot
stuff microservices story and you'll see
微服务的故事，您会看到
margins going to show you some cool
利润率会告诉你一些酷
demos with that in a little while let's
演示一下，让我们
talk about to bring boot yes our focus
谈论带靴子是我们的重点
at the moment is to make it very easy to
此刻是使其非常容易
write the right to bring boot to write
写权带开机写
spring boot apps the right way and get
spring boot 应用程序的正确方法并获得
them work with them especially in a
他们与他们合作，尤其是在
micro services setup where you've got a
微服务设置
number of them you're working on at the
您正在其中工作的人数
same time now Chris and Martin you're
现在同一时间，克里斯和马丁，你是
going to show you some pretty
给你看一些漂亮的东西
comprehensive workflow so you can go
全面的工作流程，因此您可以
through with that stuff I'm going to
通过这些东西，我要去
talk a little bit about some stuff that
谈一些有关的东西
doesn't quite fit into that but it'll
不太适合那个，但它会
give you an idea of the kinds of things
让你对事物的想法
we're working on at the moment I would
我们现在正在努力
encourage you if you get time or you
鼓励你，如果有时间或者你
haven't read them already go and have a
还没看过书就走了
look at the new and noteworthy for the
看看新的和值得关注的
releases then you may see an eclipse
释放，然后您可能会看到日食
release come out and assume well that
发布出来，并假设
looks like the last thing release of
看起来像是最后发布的
clips if you actually go in the new and
剪辑，如果您实际使用新的
know whether you'll see all the new cool
知道你是否会看到所有新的酷
stuff that's in there so if you look at
里面的东西，所以如果你看
what they've changed for the Java tools
他们对Java工具所做的更改
there's things like this substring code
像这样的子字符串代码
completion so you can just type in
完成，因此您只需输入
partial pieces of a name and when you
部分名称以及当您
ask for content assist you get all the
要求内容帮助您获得所有
words with that end rather than just the
那个目的的话，而不仅仅是
ones that start with it there was some
以它开头的
of that in the previous release given to
在以前的版本中
you by code recommenders but now it's a
通过代码推荐者，但现在是
first-class feature in JDT they've added
他们添加了JDT中的一流功能
some new stuff around templates you'll
模板周围的一些新内容
see that we're also doing some stuff
看到我们也在做一些事情
around templates I'll get on to more
关于模板，我将继续介绍
refactoring stuff to enable you to do
重构东西，使您能够做
things faster like when you create a
像创建一个
method with a number of parameters you
带有多个参数的方法
can immediately with a quick fix just
可以立即进行快速修复
create fields for all those parameters
为所有这些参数创建字段
you don't have to do them one at a time
您不必一次做一个
not you used to have things like search
以前你没有像搜索这样的东西
you used to be out of search on one
你曾经是一个人
thing at a time you now can select
现在一次可以选择的东西
multiple things press that search and it
多件事按那个搜索，它
will show you the results of finding all
将向您显示查找所有结果
those things but it's not just things in
这些东西，但不仅仅是其中的东西
the JDT section if you look in the the
JDT部分，如果您在
platform section there's stuff that can
平台部分中有可以
help you when you're right in Java some
当您正确使用Java时可以为您提供帮助
people get excited about this feature I
人们对此功能感到兴奋
am NOT one of those people but you now
不是那些人之一，但你现在
have wordwrap in your in your text
在您的文字中使用自动换行
editors for people who need that kind of
需要这类内容的人的编辑
thing let me just show you that there's
事情让我告诉你
a key binding but there's also this
一个键绑定，但也有这个
button up here so you're limited on
在这里按一下，这样您就可以
space rather than losing it you can
空间，而不是失去它，你可以
actually see what's on that next line oh
其实看看下一行是什么哦
yeah
是的
is what sorry I can't quite hear you
是对不起我听不到您的声音
merge conflicts
合并冲突
I haven't seen any enhancements to make
我还没有看到任何增强功能
that easier I usually rely on get to do
我通常依靠做起来更容易
the right thing you were of any changes
您所做的任何更改都是正确的
to me the question was whether than any
对我来说，问题是
enhancements to merge conflicts but I'm
合并冲突的增强功能，但我
not aware of any but have a read through
不知道任何但已通读
here it might be tucked away somewhere
在这里它可能藏在某个地方
there's a lot of stuff in here so yeah
这里有很多东西，是的
and alongside that of course within when
当然还有什么时候
we do it release we also produce a new
我们发布它，我们也产生一个新的
noteworthy now SDS doesn't have
现在值得注意的是，SDS还没有
comprehensive docks somewhere what we
综合码头在我们所处的地方
have is a new noteworthy where we really
有一个新的值得注意的地方
go into detail on how to use some of
详细介绍如何使用
these features so you'll see there's
这些功能，所以您会看到
pages and pages of stuff I'm not going
一页和几页我不会去的东西
to go through all this because you're
去经历所有这一切，因为你
going to see real live demos from Chris
看克里斯的真实现场演示
and Martin that's just a couple of
和马丁这只是几个
things I wanted to touch on so I showed
我想讲的东西，所以我展示了
you that JDT itself is adding some
您，JDT本身正在添加一些
templates we are also starting to do
我们也开始做的模板
more work around templates to enable you
围绕模板进行更多工作以使您能够
to write this is about when I talked
写这是关于我说话的时候
about originally about writing good
关于最初关于写好
spring boot code so if you follow the
spring boot 代码，所以如果您遵循
template use the templates you'll end up
模板使用您将最终得到的模板
following the patterns of how people
遵循人们的方式
recommend you should write to bring boo
建议您写信带嘘
coupled with that let's jump into STS
加上这一点，让我们跳入STS
just got this little demo application
刚得到这个小演示应用程序
something's always annoyed me is that
总是让我烦恼的是
the content assist for static imports
内容有助于静态导入
just was it just didn't work out of the
只是它没有起作用而已
box and I felt like it should so now if
盒子，我觉得现在应该这样
you're in a test and you start this is a
你正在测试中，你开始这是一个
spring boot app I created with a starter
我用启动器创建的Spring Boot应用程序
wizard if you start doing things like a
向导，如果您开始执行类似
cert true and content assist on that you
证明真实，内容对您有帮助
get the content assist this is a miracle
获得内容协助，这是一个奇迹
that works out of the box and that's
开箱即用，那就是
because we're doing some work for you
因为我们正在为您做一些工作
managing the content assist favorites I
管理内容辅助收藏夹I
mean maybe you didn't know that in order
意思是也许你不知道这是为了
to get content assist in Eclipse for
在Eclipse中获得内容帮助
static imports you need to add them to
静态导入，您需要将其添加到
this list for it to work so what we've
该列表使其正常工作，所以我们已经
done is we've added them all for you
完成了，我们已经为您添加了它们
based on what we recommend you use for
根据我们建议您使用的
spring boo I would encourage you if you
春天嘘，我会鼓励你，如果你
find some others that you use all the
找到一些你用的所有
time and maybe other people use all the
时间，也许其他人会使用所有
time let us know we can maybe add them
时间让我们知道我们可以添加它们
in so now you'll find these just work
在这里，您现在会发现这些功能确实有效
out of the box so it's all about making
开箱即用，这就是制作
it easier and faster to write to bring
编写起来更容易，更快捷
good boot code
良好的启动代码
another convenience feature if you do
如果您愿意的话，另一个便利功能
refactoring rename so I've got an
重构重命名，所以我有一个
application here alongside I've got some
我这里有一些应用程序
tests for that application if I rename
如果我重命名，则测试该应用程序
the application its call it foo
该应用程序将其称为foo
application I get a warning because it's
应用程序我收到警告，因为它是
got a main method in that's fine but
有一个主要的方法，但是很好
you'll see now you get a pop-up saying
您会看到现在弹出窗口说
you rename that do you also want to
您重命名，您也想
rename your tests that will save you
重命名可以节省您的测试
some time so to click yes you see my
一段时间，所以单击是，您会看到我的
tests are also rename just we're doing a
测试也被重命名，只是我们正在做一个
lot of these little convenience features
这些便利功能很多
so you can work faster a couple of pet
这样你可以更快地养几个宠物
ones that I want to cover this is where
我想介绍的是
and you probably hit it too you're
而且你可能也击中了
working in Eclipse and you press control
在Eclipse中工作，然后按控制
space and it does you can't understand
空间，你不明白吗
why it isn't telling you the right thing
为什么它没有告诉你正确的事情
as an example here we have here I've got
作为一个例子，我们这里有
in this in this other folder I've got an
在另一个文件夹中，我有一个
interface pretty straightforward and
界面非常简单，
I've got a implementation of that this
我已经实现了这一点
is just a plain eclipse I'm going to
只是我要去的蚀
create an instance and I'm going to
创建一个实例，我要
press the ctrl space here where's my
按ctrl空间，这是我的
implementation it's right there it's
实施就在那里
like four lines away in a package
像包装中的四行
Explorer why can't the content assist
资源管理器为何无法提供帮助
see it those kinds of frustrations slow
看到那些挫折缓慢
you down so what we're doing in sts is
您下来，所以我们在sts中所做的是
that where we're fixing some of these
我们正在修复其中一些问题的地方
things so if I to go and do the same
所以如果我去做同样的事情
thing in my crew application
在我的乘务员申请中
I get my implementation suggestion so I
我得到了实施建议，所以我
would encourage you again if you if you
如果你愿意的话会再次鼓励你
get frustrated with the clips just
只是对剪辑感到沮丧
before you throw the computer out the
在将计算机扔出之前
window use it to raise a jira against us
窗户用它来对我们提出吉拉
and we can maybe fix that for you let us
我们也许可以为您修复该问题，让我们
know another case that drives me
知道另一个驱使我的情况
particularly crazy I've got here a list
特别疯狂，我在这里有一个清单
factory so I'm going to use my factory
工厂，所以我要用我的工厂
class it's got a method I give me a list
课上有一种方法，我给我一个清单
of now I am at this time got list
现在我在这个时候得到清单
imported let me jump over to this method
导入让我跳过此方法
it seems pretty clear to me what that
对我来说，这很清楚
returns com example foo list but if I go
返回com示例foo列表，但如果我去
and try and in my application do quick
并尝试在我的应用程序中快速执行
fix java.awt list clearly that is not
修复java.awt列表显然不是
what I want and somewhere down here a
我想要的东西在这里某处
few pages away is my one that I want now
几页远就是我现在想要的那一页
I would have thought it was pretty
我本以为这很漂亮
obvious which one I wanted so what we're
很明显我想要哪一个，所以我们
doing is fixing that in it sts so if i
这样做是修复它的STS，所以如果我
do the same thing here my list factory
我的清单工厂在这里做同样的事情
don't give me a list quick fix it's the
不要给我一个快速修复的清单，这是
first one on the list and i like this
名单上的第一个，我喜欢这个
its work flow of quick fix press return
快速修复印刷机的工作流程
to accept the first one bam bam bam bam
接受第一个bam bam bam bam
you just keep on working so those are
你只是继续努力，所以
the kinds of quality of life
生活质量的种类
improvements we're putting in so you can
我们正在进行的改进，以便您可以
be more productive so if you've got any
提高生产力，如果有的话
of those any frustrations let us know so
这些挫折中的一个让我们知道
those were a couple of things that
那是几件事
didn't quite fit into the workflow so
不太适合工作流程，所以
the other guys going to do but I'm going
其他人会做，但我要
to hand it back to Chris now and he is
现在把它交给克里斯，他是
going to win though take us through a
要赢，虽然带我们经历了一个
full workflow of using some other
使用其他功能的完整工作流程
features that I am touched on that are
我感动的功能是
in that new and noteworthy I encourage
在这个新的值得注意的地方，我鼓励
you to go and read it Chris
你去读克里斯
so i'm going to show you now is I'm
所以我现在要告诉你是我
going to show you how to work with
会告诉你如何使用
spring boot applications locally and how
Spring Boot应用程序本地以及如何
to work with micro services in
与微服务一起工作
particular so the idea here is that if
特别是这里的想法是，如果
you're working with microservices you
您正在使用微服务
probably have more than one right so the
可能拥有不止一项权利，所以
point of having microservices pro you
微服务对您的好处
have lots of them and what the tools are
有很多，什么是工具
trying to do here is give you a way to
尝试在这里做的是给你一种方法
work with the subset of the applications
处理应用程序的子集
in your workspace so that you can focus
在您的工作区中，以便您可以集中精力
on the ones that you're interested in so
对您感兴趣的
the thing that you see here is the
您在这里看到的是
spring boot dashboard it's something we
spring boot 仪表板这是我们的事情
showed you last year as well and I'm not
去年也给你看过，我不是
going to show you as much of it this
会向你展示尽可能多的东西
time but I'm just going to quickly show
时间，但我只是要快速展示
you a few things so the application that
你几件事，所以应用程序
I'm working with is a chat application
我正在使用的是聊天应用程序
I'm going to show you a demo with that
我将向您展示一个演示
and work with that and I just type at
并使用它，我只输入
the top here chatter and it matches on
顶部这里chat不休，它与
the name of the application or a tag
应用程序名称或标签
that you attach to it and that way i can
你依附于它，这样我就可以
very flexibly sort of work with a subset
非常灵活地处理子集
and of course if you have lots of
当然，如果您有很多
applications you probably want to run
您可能要运行的应用程序
lots of applications if you want to do
很多应用程序，如果你想做
that in eclipse it can be a little bit
在日食中可能会有点
tedious but if you do that with a spring
乏味，但如果您春天来了
booth dashboard you just click on this
展位仪表板，您只需单击此
button and that's it all your
按钮，仅此而已
applications are starting so let's have
应用程序正在启动，所以让我们有
a quick look at what we're running here
快速浏览一下我们在这里运行的内容
or you can also see the console is going
或者您也可以看到控制台正在运行
here and of course I have lots of
在这里，当然我有很多
applications I probably have a few
我可能有几个应用
consoles with the output and there's
控制台的输出，有
something weird going on okay let's
发生了一些奇怪的事情，让我们
ignore that I hope that's not going to
忽略我希望那不会
cause me any problems but we'll see yeah
给我造成任何问题，但我们会看到的
so you can see the the consoles here if
因此，您可以在此处查看控制台
you click if you click on this button
如果您单击此按钮，则单击
here you can switch quickly between the
在这里您可以在
different consoles and let's stick with
不同的控制台，让我们坚持
the chatter log for now or let's chatter
现在聊天记录，或者让我们聊天
log it's one of the interesting ones
记录它是有趣的之一
this this particular one here chatter
这个这个特别的人在这里chat不休
web UI is my user interface and you see
Web UI是我的用户界面，您会看到
that next to each one you see this
在每个旁边，您会看到这个
number that's the port that it's running
这是它正在运行的端口号
on
上
so these ports are randomly chosen by
因此这些端口是由
spring boot so it's particularly useful
spring boot ，因此特别有用
at ec them you don't have to scan your
在ec他们，您不必扫描您的
console output to find where this you
控制台输出找到您所在的位置
just double click on this and it will
只需双击它，它将
open in the web browser so this is my
在网络浏览器中打开，所以这是我的
application here now this is most of
现在在这里应用
this is not new but what's new this one
这不是什么新东西，但是这是什么新东西
of the things that's new that I want to
我想要的新事物
highlight here is we now support running
这里的重点是我们现在支持跑步
multiple instances of the same thing
同一件事的多个实例
which might be useful if you're testing
如果您正在测试，这可能会很有用
something with scaling or something
有缩放的东西
locally so for example let's say I want
在本地，例如，假设我要
to run another instance of this web UI
运行此Web UI的另一个实例
what do I do well right click and then
我该怎么办右键单击然后
duplicate my launch configuration and
复制我的启动配置，然后
now you see that this expands here and I
现在您看到它在这里扩展，我
have to launch configurations for the
必须启动配置
same thing I can edit it and change it a
我可以编辑并更改它
little bit so I open my launch
一点点，所以我打开我的发射
configuration and notice we have some
配置并注意我们有一些
nice content this is there I use server
不错的内容，这是我使用的服务器
that port and run this on a different
该端口并在其他端口上运行
port because I cannot run the two
端口，因为我无法运行两者
instances on the same port that wouldn't
在同一端口上的实例
work right so change the port and save
工作正常，因此更改端口并保存
this and I can now launch this and now
这个，现在我可以启动这个
you can see also if I collapse this you
你也可以看看我是否折叠了你
can still see the information summarized
仍然可以看到信息摘要
here there's two things running two out
这里有两件事用完了
of two on two different ports and I can
两个不同的端口上的两个，我可以
also double-click it and you see now I
也双击它，你现在看到我
have two two versions of my application
有我的应用程序的两个两个版本
running one on port 8080 11 on port 8080
在端口8080上运行一个11在端口8080上运行
and of course they are connected because
当然他们是因为
it's a chap application how they're
这是一个章应用程序
connected I might get into this a little
连接我可能会有点
bit later but behind the scenes here
稍晚一点，但在幕后
this uses RabbitMQ and sprinkled streams
这使用RabbitMQ和洒水流
so all my little web services here are
所以我这里所有的小网络服务都是
talking to each other over rabbitmq so
通过rabbitmq互相交谈
that's how these two web UI instances
这就是这两个Web UI实例的方式
are actually connected even though
实际上已经连接
they're separate processes okay so
他们是独立的流程，所以
that's about all I wanted to show you
那就是我想给你看的
for now about the booth dashboard itself
现在关于展位仪表板本身
so are we going to do next
那我们下一步要做吗
I'm going to build a new micro service
我要建立一个新的微服务
from scratch and add it to this
从头开始并将其添加到此
application and what I'm going to do is
应用程序，我要做的是
I'm going to build a little chatter bot
我要建立一个聊天机器人
something that sends messages every so
总是这样发送消息的东西
often just sending messages so that
通常只是发送消息，以便
should be pretty simple so how we do
应该很简单，所以我们该怎么做
that let's start by creating a new
让我们从创建一个新的开始
application here's new spring starter
应用在这里是新的弹簧启动器
project and give it a name it's already
项目并给它起个名字
filled in because i did this demo a few
填写是因为我做了这个演示
times so it's remembered what i wanted
次，所以想起了我想要的
to do pick and pick a boot version and
做一个引导版本，然后
then pick some starters so i'm not going
然后选择一些开胃菜，所以我不去
to dwell too much on this because you've
在这个问题上讲太多，因为你已经
probably seen this kind of thing before
大概以前看过这种东西
this is like the initializer app that
这就像初始化程序
you might have seen on the web we have a
您可能已经在网上看到了
front end for that basically so I pick
基本上是前端，所以我选择
my starters we have an actuator and the
首先，我们有一个执行器，
rabbit one is the spring cloud streams
兔子一是春天的云流
that's how my micro services are all
这就是我所有的微服务
connected so that's what i want so
连接，所以这就是我想要的
finish and you see that there is a new
完成后，您会发现有一个新
app that appeared here and it appeared
出现在这里的应用程序，它出现了
over there as well i can serve open in
我也可以在那边开放
package Explorer and I can start coding
包资源管理器，我可以开始编码
right away okay so here's my application
马上好，这是我的申请
we're going to use spring cloud streams
我们将使用春季云流
so to enable that you use an annotation
这样就可以使用注释
enable binding and it has a parameter
启用绑定，它具有一个参数
this parameter is a interface which
此参数是一个接口
basically defines the communication
基本上定义了沟通
protocol that your app has with the rest
您的应用与其他协议所拥有的协议
of the code through the through the
通过的代码
spring cloud streams and i'm going to
春天的云流，我要去
use source class because what I'm
使用源类，因为我是
implementing is just a stupid little bot
实现只是一个愚蠢的小机器人
which sends messages so it is a source
发送消息，所以它是一个来源
it just sends things it doesn't receive
它只是发送它没有收到的东西
anything once you've done that you get
一旦完成就可以得到
from spring boot and from springville
从 spring boot 和从斯普林维尔
streams you automatically get a source
流，您会自动获得来源
an instance of that class are beamed
该类的一个实例发出光芒
and we'll autowire that I'll use a
我们会自动连线，我将使用
little a very old quick quick fix that
一点点非常老的快速快速修复
we have for a long time just auto wired
我们有很长一段时间只是自动接线
okay good I want to start this but when
好吧，我想开始这个，但是当
it's when once the app is kind of
当应用程序有点像
getting started so I'll use a post
开始，所以我会用一个帖子
construct method to start my little bot
构造启动我的小机器人的方法
and I'll need something to execute
我需要一些东西来执行
something every so often so i'll use a
每隔一段时间我就用一个
task scheduler i'll call it scheduler
任务调度程序，我称它为调度程序
and i'm going to auto wire that one too
我也要自动接线
it won't work just yet because you get
这还行不通，因为您得到了
this for free but you just have to ask
这个是免费的，但是你只需要问
nicely spring boot will configure this
很好的春季引导将配置此
for you but you just have to ask nicely
为你，但你只需要问好
basically so say enable scheduling and
基本上说启用调度和
the schedule will be created and can be
时间表将被创建，可以是
injected this source class this is this
注入这个源类是这个
is a something in spring called stream
春天的东西叫做流
so i can show you what what's in there
所以我可以告诉你里面有什么
actually i think it yeah it's actually
其实我认为是的
good that you asked me because i
很好，你问我，因为我
imported the wrong source class actually
实际导入了错误的源类
let's fix that I would have a surprise
让我们修复一下，我会感到惊讶
later on that something didn't work so
后来那没用，所以
let's do i need this source class the
我们需要这个源类吗
one from spring cloud stream so what
一从春天的云流，所以
that is when you do enable binding what
那就是当您启用绑定时
spring bloodstream does it creates some
春天的血液会产生一些
infrastructure for you to wire things up
基础设施供您连接
to the back end which could be RabbitMQ
到后端可能是RabbitMQ
or Kafka or something something for
或Kafka或其他东西
messaging and in this and this defines
消息传递，在此和此定义
how you talk to it what kind of messages
你怎么跟它说话
you receive and what kind of messages
您收到什么消息
you send so a source is a communication
您发送，因此来源就是沟通
pattern where you just sending things so
您只是发送东西的模式
there is an output on that because
有一个输出，因为
you're going to send something you see
你要发送一些你看到的东西
so and the rest is all magic spring
所以剩下的就是神奇的春天
cloud stream sets that up it creates
云流设置它创建的
queues and exchanges on rabbit and queue
兔子和队列上的队列和交换
for you and it's all set up
为您而设
yeah and for receiving or transforming
是的，用于接收或转换
there are other interfaces and you can
还有其他界面，您可以
define your own as well so you can
也定义您自己的，这样您就可以
define something completely custom or
定义完全自定义的内容或
use one of those predefined ones I'm
使用我是那些预定义的
just using this because that the very
只是使用这个，因为
common pattern is that you either just a
常见的模式是，您要么只是
consumer or a sender or something that
消费者或发件人或其他
receives messages and then does
接收消息，然后执行
something and sends it back out right so
并将其发送回去，这样
for those three cases you have something
对于这三种情况，您有一些东西
if you have something more complicated
如果你有更复杂的东西
you can write it yourself where was I
你可以自己写我在哪里
yes here so we create this then we have
是的，在这里，所以我们创建这个，然后
the scheduler we can start using it and
我们可以开始使用调度程序了
I can say schedule at fixed rate I have
我可以说我有固定的时间表
two two parameters here so this one is
这里有两个两个参数，所以这个是
how many time in between three thousand
三千之间有多少时间
milliseconds let's say and here i need a
毫秒，这里我需要一个
runnable which we can use a nice lambda
可运行的，我们可以使用一个很好的lambda
expression because we're now all on Java
表达，因为我们现在都在使用Java
8 right so we'll use a nice lambda
8对，所以我们将使用一个很好的lambda
expression and now you'll see what that
表达，现在您将看到
source is because I've got that being
资料来源是因为我知道
injected so I can just use that now it's
注入，所以我现在就可以使用它了
a channel dot output and then I could
通道点输出，然后我可以
send a message on it what kind of a
在上面发送消息是什么样的
message will create the message using
消息将使用创建消息
the message builder which is also part
消息生成器，它也是一部分
of that spring cloud stream libraries
春天的云流库
with payload and the payload is what I'm
与有效载荷，有效载荷是我
going to be sending so what am I going
要发送，所以我要去
to be sending just a little ping message
仅发送一点ping消息
Oh ping
哦平
and I'll to make it more interesting
我会让它变得更有趣
I'll put a counter in it great field
我会在这个大领域里摆一个柜台
okay and it's a message builder so we
好的，这是一个消息生成器，所以我们
have to build the message let's do like
必须建立信息，让我们喜欢
this okay that's that's all there is to
好的，那就是全部
it and that should now be working so if
它现在应该可以正常工作了，如果
I'm running it now it should work
我正在运行它，它应该可以工作
actually it's not going to work that
实际上这是行不通的
will debug it a little bit later so
稍后再调试
let's see I run it let's run it oh
让我们看看我运行它吧让我们运行它哦
that's yeah I've had this problem once
是的，我曾经遇到过这个问题
before when i did my demo and i don't
在我进行演示之前，我没有
know how to solve it so eclipse and may
知道如何解决这个问题，可能会
even has done something really bad to my
甚至对我做得很不好
project and i don't know how to solve it
项目，我不知道如何解决
I I'll try something which I've never
我会尝试一些我从未尝试过的东西
tried before
尝试过
yeah you know what I'm going to cheat ok
是的，你知道我要作弊吗
sorry i'll just copy this delete
抱歉，我只会复制此删除内容
closed projects
封闭项目
here
这里
okay let's see if it if it works this
好吧，让我们看看它是否可行
time all right sorry for the disruption
好的，抱歉打扰了
that was there's a bug somewhere that we
那是我们某个地方的错误
have to figure out with them so my app
必须找出他们，所以我的应用程序
is running but as you can oh yeah sorry
正在运行，但您可以哦，对不起
I yeah I skipped the whole part of my
是的，我跳过了整个部分
workflow here let's let's delete this
这里的工作流程让我们删除它
alright
好的
stop
停
okay so when we run this you see that it
好的，所以当我们运行它时，您会看到它
didn't get started there was a problem
没有开始存在问题
with it now this problem was actually
现在，这个问题实际上是
expected so i'm not running it on the
预期的，所以我没有在
right port so what I have to do is I
正确的端口，所以我要做的就是
have to configure the port so you saw
必须配置端口，以便您看到
that I did that earlier in the launch
我在发布初期就做了
configuration you can also do that in
配置，您也可以在
your application of properties file we
您的属性文件申请我们
give you an editor for either the Amal
给您Amal的编辑
or the properties format you can use
或您可以使用的属性格式
either one which you like best I'm going
我最喜欢的一个
to use the AMOLED eter and we get nice
使用AMOLED测距仪，我们会感觉很好
content assist in there so if i do a
内容协助在那里，所以如果我做一个
server that port and i do this and then
服务器该端口，我这样做，然后
i can just fill in the number when i put
我放的时候可以填写数字
0 that basically means to spring boot
0基本上意味着启动弹簧
i'll pick that dynamically okay another
我会动态地选择另一个
thing which i did which I kind of
我做过的事
skipped because of all the mess is I've
因为所有的混乱而跳过了
added spring boot devtools do this so
添加了spring boot devtools这样做
there is a few ways you could do that
有几种方法可以做到这一点
the easiest way would be go right in
最简单的方法就是直接进入
this menu here spring tools and there is
这个菜单在这里，spring tool，还有
a menu there to add boot dev tools and
那里的菜单添加启动开发工具和
right now it says remove because I've
现在它说删除，因为我已经
already added it but you could have
已经添加了，但是您可以
added that way what bhudev stools does
用这种方式补充了bhudev的凳子功能
you'll see you'll see shortly I'll just
你会看到你会很快看到我会
I'll just show you when it actually does
我会告诉你它什么时候实际发生
something so we let's run this app again
一些东西，让我们再次运行这个应用程序
I'll start it up okay
我会开始的
and you see that nothing is actually
你会发现实际上什么都没有
happening in my user 8 interface here I
发生在我的用户8界面中
was expecting some messages I don't see
期待一些我看不到的消息
them so let's try to figure out what is
他们，所以让我们尝试找出是什么
wrong with it so let's go to yeah this
错了，所以我们去吧
is another thing that shouldn't be there
是不应该存在的另一件事
yet so i'll delete that too sorry so
但我会删除那太抱歉了
here is my chatter ping bot so if we
这是我的聊天机器人，如果我们
want to figure out what's going wrong
想找出出什么问题了
maybe some debug messages would help so
也许一些调试消息会有所帮助
let's add some debug messages will need
让我们添加一些需要的调试消息
a logger and like Andy said we've added
一个记录器，就像安迪所说，我们已经添加了
some templates and one of those
一些模板，其中之一
templates is a pattern for the typical
模板是典型的模式
self forge a logger so you just expand
自己打造一个记录器，这样您就可以扩展
the template here and you get what the
模板在这里，你会得到什么
spring boot developers would recommend
Spring Boot开发人员会推荐
you write to create a logger so that's
你写来创建一个记录器，所以
this this pattern here and then I can
这种模式在这里，然后我可以
also use it we have some templates for
也使用它，我们有一些模板
using it as well so the bar blog message
也使用它，所以酒吧博客消息
you would do like this and I can say
你会喜欢的，我可以说
starting bing bot and then we can do
启动bing bot，然后我们可以做
here another message saying sending OOP
在这里另一条消息说发送OOP
sending message okay and you see did you
发送消息好，你知道吗
see that there was some activity here in
看到这里有一些活动
the console so that's what spring boot
控制台，这就是 spring boot
devtools was doing so it's like a tool
devtools在这样做，就像工具一样
that helps you more easily and quickly
可以帮助您更轻松，更快速地
develop whenever you see a little
只要看到一点就发展
whenever it sees a change in your
每当看到您的变化
project it will automatically start it
项目，它将自动启动它
in the background your app will be
在后台您的应用程序将
quickly restarted so that's what
快速重启，这就是
happened here I still don't see any
发生在这里我仍然看不到任何东西
debug messages though well the reason
虽然调试消息很好的原因
for that is that I need to enable debug
因为那是我需要启用调试
messages because the logging level is
消息，因为日志记录级别是
something you configure and by default
您配置的内容，默认情况下
the debug level messages are not output
调试级别消息不输出
so let's configure that
所以我们来配置
logging dot level another property that
记录点级别的另一个属性是
we can get from spring boot and we get
我们可以从 spring boot 上得到
some content assist there as well the
一些内容也有帮助
name of the logger is usually a class or
记录器的名称通常是一个类或
a package so we get content assist it
一个包，以便我们获得内容帮助
also knows what kind of things you can
也知道你可以做些什么
put there so let's put the bug and now
放在那里，让我们放个错误，现在
if I if I save this see the activity
如果我保存了，请看活动
happening here and you see that my debug
发生在这里，你看到我的调试
messages are coming out so my debugging
消息出来，所以我的调试
messages are now configured that's just
消息现在已配置
well the ideas with the debugger this is
调试器的想法是
self forge a logger right so it's a
自我伪造一个记录器的权利，所以它是一个
logging facility you when you ship your
运送工具时，您便可以使用
code you probably don't want all those
代码，您可能不想要所有这些
debug messages on but when you're
调试消息，但是当您
debugging you want them so the logger
调试您想要它们，以便记录器
allows you to turn turn on selectively
允许您有选择地打开
on or off your logging messages so like
打开或关闭您的日志记录消息，例如
when your app is deployed and there is
当您的应用程序部署并且
something going wrong with some
有些东西出了问题
properties that you can change you can
可以更改的属性可以
just turn on logging for specific class
只需打开特定班级的日志记录
and see what's going on in there right
看看那里发生了什么
now it's in the classpath but there are
现在在类路径中，但是有
different ways that so that's that's
不同的方式，那就是
actually a spring boot of a spring booth
实际上是一个弹簧棚的 spring boot
thing so in spring boot it it gets these
东西，所以在 spring boot 它得到这些
properties from many different places so
来自许多不同地方的物业
one place it can get it from is from
一个可以得到它的地方是
these files in your classpath another
这些文件在您的类路径中
place you can get it from is from
你可以从那里得到它的地方
environment variables another place the
环境变量另一个地方
system properties so there are many
系统属性，所以有很多
places you can basically change these
基本上可以改变这些地方
things so you can have some stuff
东西，所以你可以有一些东西
packaged into your app but you can still
打包到您的应用中，但您仍然可以
override them from the outside through
从外面覆盖它们
an environment variable or something
环境变量之类的
like that yeah yes so but we're still so
是的，是的，但是我们仍然如此
we seeing that these debug messages show
我们看到这些调试消息显示
is that it's actually working they are
是实际上它在起作用
being sent but they are not arriving
被发送但他们没有到达
here so something is still not there
这里有些东西仍然不存在
okay so let's fix that
好吧，让我们修复一下
that the problem is we have to configure
问题是我们必须配置
where the messages are going they have
消息去向何处
to go to the right channel in the rabbit
去兔子右边的通道
and Q back end basically so if you look
和Q后端，所以如果你看
again at the source class if I go back
如果我回去，再次在源类上
there and look at this source class
在那里，看看这个源类
there is a identifier here output and
这里有一个标识符输出
this is the name of that channel the
这是该频道的名称
name of that thing and I need to bind
那东西的名字，我需要绑定
that to a specific thing a specific Q in
对特定事物的特定Q in
rabbitmq so let's do that again we can
rabbitmq，让我们再做一次，我们可以
do that through these configuration
通过这些配置来做到这一点
properties these bindings so this is a
属性这些绑定，所以这是一个
binding so i type binding you see that
绑定，所以我键入绑定，您会看到
my content assist suggests these things
我的内容帮助提示了这些事情
here this is the one I want spring
这是我想要的春天
plowed stream bindings so let's get that
犁流绑定，让我们得到
and if I kind of click here you can see
如果我单击此处，您可以看到
what that is too we can jump to the code
那也可以跳转到代码
and you see that's a map of string and
而且您看到的是字符串映射，
then a bunch of properties and this
然后是一堆属性
string is the name of that channel so
字符串是该频道的名称，因此
output right now I don't get I don't get
现在输出我不明白我不明白
the nice content assist for that because
好的内容有助于实现这一目标，因为
that's just a string so I have to tie
那只是一串，所以我必须系
that here I type output and then once
我在这里输入输出然后输入一次
i'm there i still i get the content
我在那儿我还是得到内容
assist for these properties that are
协助这些属性
inside there and what i want to do is
在里面，我想做的是
set the destination to chat because the
设置聊天的目的地，因为
name chat is what i used for all my
聊天是我所有的习惯
communication with my application okay
与我的应用程序通信可以
so we set the destination of that to
所以我们将目的地设置为
chat I save it and now you see that the
聊天我将其保存，现在您看到
bing bot is working it's sending the
bing机器人正在运行，正在发送
messages you see them appear sorry
您看到的邮件出现对不起
that's just a name yeah that's the same
只是名字而已
name I used in all the other ones so so
我在其他所有名称中都使用过的名称
in rabbitmq there are some exchanges and
在rabbitmq有一些交流，
Q's created and that's the name of that
Q的创建就是那个的名字
thing it's a it's a resource basically
基本上是资源
somewhere in the in RabbitMQ where i can
我可以在RabbitMQ中的某个地方
send messages and receive messages from
从发送消息和接收消息
right so and with Spring cloud stream I
是的，并且有了Spring cloud stream我
defined it you have these
定义它你有这些
this pattern here you you have to map
这种模式在这里你必须要映射
these outputs and inputs to specific
这些输出和输入要具体
things on the message bus essentially
消息总线上的事物本质上
okay so you see it's all working out my
好吧，所以你看到这一切都在解决我的问题
ping bought is sending messages and they
ping购买的正在发送消息，他们
appear in the UI so it's all working the
出现在用户界面中，因此一切正常
next thing I want to show you is you
接下来我想告诉你的是你
solve this nice content assist here what
解决这个很好的内容在这里帮助什么
you mean like this port see it's it says
你的意思是说像这个港口一样
unknown property server port so there is
未知的属性服务器端口，所以有
a warning here yeah if I if I type yes
这里是一个警告，如果我输入是的话
if i type instead of a number type ABC
如果我键入而不是数字，则输入ABC
you see it says I expect an integer here
你看到它说我期望这里是一个整数
that's not good so there is some
那不好，所以有些
checking yes okay now what I want to
检查是好现在我想要什么
show you next is these properties are
接下来告诉你这些属性是
baked in sort of to spring boot and we
烤到 spring boot ，我们
get nice content assist for that but you
得到很好的内容帮助，但是您
can also get that for your own
也可以自己拿
configuration and that's what i want to
配置，这就是我想要的
show you next how do you set it up so
接下来向您展示如何设置它
that you get the same nice content
你得到同样好的内容
assist for your own configuration
协助您自己的配置
properties so what we're going to do
属性，所以我们要做什么
next is I'm going to fix something in
接下来是我要修复的东西
this spring this bot here it's got some
今年春天，这个机器人在这里
hard coded stuff in it that we don't
硬编码的东西，我们不
like so let's make that configurable so
像这样让我们使它可配置
what I want to do is make a property
我想要做的是做一个财产
called name for the name of the user of
被称为name的用户名
this bot so that it can say here the
这个机器人，以便它可以在这里说
name of the user instead of just thing
用户名，而不是唯一的东西
and that it can use the interval that we
它可以使用我们的间隔
can configure that so how do we do that
可以配置它，那么我们该怎么做
we'll just create a new class for these
我们将为此创建一个新类
properties will call that class ping
属性将调用该类ping
properties
属性
and then we add an annotation called
然后添加一个名为
Atkins at con add configuration
Atkins at con add配置
properties you put a prefix there so the
属性，您在其中放置前缀，因此
name of my at this app is chatter and
我在这个应用程式中的名字是chat不休，
the properties are all about this pink
属性都是关于这个粉红色的
thing so i'll call them chatter dropping
事情，所以我称他们为chat不休
all my properties will start with this
我所有的财产都会以此开始
shattered thing dot something and i will
破碎的东西点点东西，我会
make a user property and i will make a
创建一个用户属性，我将创建一个
property for the time between things and
物与物之间的时间属性
another good thing to do is get default
另一件事是默认
values so the default values are so that
值，因此默认值是
if i don't configure them things still
如果我不配置它们，事情还是
work and have sensible defaults right so
工作并具有明智的默认设置，因此
if i don't configure anything my app
如果我没有配置我的应用程序
will still work so let's put that
仍然可以工作，所以让我们
another good thing to do is put some
另一件事是做一些
comments the comments are documentation
评论评论是文档
and they will show up also in the in the
他们也会出现在
UI in the editor so it's good to put
编辑器中的UI，因此最好放置
something useful here so let's say the
这里有用的东西，所以说
name used in the message and this one is
消息中使用的名称，这是
the time between messages in
消息之间的时间间隔
milliseconds okay and you see a few
毫秒还可以，您会看到一些
squigglies actually there is one
弯曲的实际上有一个
squiggly that is missing I'll just skip
迷失的是我会跳过
over that so i'll just create some
在那上面，我将创建一些
getters and setters for this that's just
为此的吸气剂和塞特剂
a standard eclipse quick fix and there
标准的日食快速修复
is one thing that i didn't that yeah so
是我没有做到这一点的一件事
i'm just going to skip over that
我只是跳过
actually so yeah I've get-togethers in
实际上，是的，我在这里聚会
the setters and now everything should be
二传手，现在一切都应该
working there is some metadata that's
工作中有一些元数据
get generated by a spring boot
由 spring boot 产生
annotation processor normally I'd have
我通常会有注释处理器
to add them because of the little
因为很少而添加它们
kerfuffle in the beginning there it's
在一开始的kerfuffle
already added now so let's just skip
现在已经添加了，所以我们就跳过
over explain
过度解释
that for an hour but and we
一个小时，但我们
automatically get content assist here so
在这里自动获得内容帮助，因此
if i type ping I'll get content assist
如果我键入ping，我将获得内容帮助
for these properties as you can see
您可以看到这些属性
chatter ping I can say chatter ping time
can平我可以说chat平时间
and also also here like you asked
就像你问的一样
earlier if i type ABC it's wrong because
早些时候，如果我输入ABC，那是错误的，因为
it's not a number and it's declared as
它不是数字，而是声明为
long so it automatically knows that it
很长，所以它会自动知道
should be a number so we'll put some
应该是一个数字，所以我们将一些
shorter time here so we'll see something
这里的时间较短，所以我们会看到一些
interesting user i'll call this user foo
有趣的用户，我称这个用户为foo
okay now you'll notice it's reloading
好吧，现在您会注意到它正在重新加载
that you don't see any real effect on
你看不到任何真正的影响
the UI of course that's that's to be
UI就是这样
expected because just defining
预期，因为仅定义
properties doesn't make them be used
属性不会使它们被使用
right so we also actually have to use
对，所以我们实际上也必须使用
them and how do you use them well enable
它们以及如何很好地使用它们
configuration properties and then we
配置属性，然后我们
need to put this class in here Bing
需要把这堂课放在这里
properties class okay and then you can
属性类好，然后您就可以
autowire that just like any other beam
像其他光束一样自动接线
so we ought to wire that beam and we can
所以我们应该连接那根光束，我们可以
use it
用它
what was the question
问题是什么
there are different ways to activate
有多种激活方式
that so another way to do it is just to
所以另一种方法是
make sure you have to make sure that
确保您必须确保
spring boot knows that it has to create
Spring Boot知道必须创建
a beam for that so one way another way
为此的光束，另一种方式
that you can do it is just to annotate
您可以做的只是注释
that glass with add component and that
带有添加成分的玻璃杯
would also work but if you annotate it
也可以，但是如果您注释它
with add component that means that
与添加组件意味着
anybody who puts that glass on the
任何将玻璃杯放在
classpath will automatically get it
classpath会自动获取它
right it's it's a little bit it depends
对，这取决于它的一点点
on what you want so you can have you
在你想要的东西上，所以你可以拥有你
have some flexibility there what was I
有一些灵活性，我当时在做什么
doing oh yeah Bing dot okay and now it's
哦，是的，Bing点好了，现在
reloading see it works okay do I have
重新加载看看它能正常工作吗
time for my last thing or do we want to
时间是我的最后一件事，还是我们想
switch just the deprecated okay so the
切换不赞成使用的行，这样
last thing I want to show you is yeah
我想告诉你的最后一件事是
no this is not hot swap this is spring
不，这不是热插拔，这是春天
boot devtools it's a a more of a class
启动devtools，这是一个更多的类
loader trick so it basically reloads
加载技巧，因此基本上可以重新加载
your classes all of them almost all of
您的课程几乎全部
them not exactly all of them but for
他们不完全是他们，而是
practical speaking let's say it reloads
实际来说，可以说它重新加载
all your classes and we start your app
您所有的课程，我们开始您的应用
so it's not java hot swap it's a it's a
所以这不是Java热插拔，而是
feature from spring boot provided by
由Spring Boot提供的功能
spring boot cheap version of j rebel
j rebel的 spring boot 便宜版
basically
基本上
yes essentially yes it restarts it's
是的，基本上是的，它重新启动它是
like you would have just killed the app
就像您刚刚杀死了该应用程序
and restarted it almost except it's a
并重新启动它，除了它是一个
little bit more efficient because it
效率更高一点，因为它
reuses the JVM and a big portion of your
重用JVM和您的很大一部分
classes that probably never changed like
可能从未改变过的类
the whole spring framework and things
整个春季框架和事物
like that
像那样
yeah the dev tools are a part in your
是的，开发工具是您的一部分
project they're there in the poem
计划他们在诗里
actually it's just a dependency that's
实际上，这只是一个依赖
all it is no no you can use it on a
所有这一切都不是不，您可以在
command line two it's it's just it's
命令行二就是这样
it's really a feature of the application
这确实是应用程序的功能
built into it now because this part of
现在内置在其中，因为
your it's on the classpath of the
你在它的类路径上
project and it's the project itself
项目本身就是项目本身
doing this this is actually not our
这样做实际上不是我们的
tools in a way we just we just added
我们刚刚添加的工具
some features to the you I've to make it
我必须要具备的一些功能
easy for you to use but but you can use
易于使用，但可以使用
it on the command line just as well but
在命令行上也一样，但是
I think I have to move on because
我认为我必须继续前进，因为
otherwise we're going to run out of time
否则我们会用光时间
before so let me just do one more last
之前让我再做一遍
little thing which is I want to show you
我想给你看的小东西
a quick fix with deprecated property so
使用已弃用属性的快速修复，因此
i'm going to show you what you would do
我要告诉你你会怎么做
if you want to make a property
如果你想做一个财产
deprecated so let's say I choose a wrong
不推荐使用，所以说我选错了
name here I didn't want to call this
在这里命名我不想叫这个
time but I want to call this interval
时间，但我想打电话给这个间隔
and I don't want to break the existing
我不想破坏现有的
code so I'm going to deprecate the old
代码，所以我将弃用旧的
property and add a new one so the best
属性，并添加一个新的，最好的
way to do that is just rename this and
要做的就是重命名这个
the trick is only rename the fields but
诀窍是仅重命名字段，但
don't rename the Gators in the setter so
不要在设置器中重命名鳄鱼
just keep those and that will keep
只要保留那些，那将保持
things backwards compatible because you
事情向后兼容，因为你
can still use the old getters and
仍然可以使用旧的吸气剂和
setters and now we add some new getters
设置器，现在我们添加了一些新的获取器
and setters okay there so now I have
和二传手好吧，现在我有了
equivalent getters and setters just
等效的获取器和设置器
different names a single property and we
不同名称的单个属性，我们
mark the old property as deprecated and
将旧属性标记为已弃用，并且
the way that works is the one that you
工作的方式就是你
have to mark is the Gator that's how
必须标记的是鳄鱼
spring boots deals with that you could
spring boot 可以解决
mark the other ones too if you want but
如果需要，也可以标记其他
you don't that's not important the one
你不认为那不重要
that matters is the Gator so sorry
重要的是鳄鱼很抱歉
deprecated it right so you could
不推荐使用它，这样您就可以
java.lang deprecated but it's better to
不推荐使用java.lang，但最好
use the one from spring boots because
使用 spring boot 中的一个，因为
you get to add a little bit of extra
你会添加一些额外的东西
information there like a reason say bad
那里的信息像一个原因，说不好
name
名称
okay you can make it you can make a more
好吧，你可以做到，你可以做更多
lengthy explanation but I don't have
冗长的解释，但我没有
time for that so and the other thing
时间如此，另一件事
that you can put is a replacement and
您可以放的是替代品，
basically I can say this thing is now
基本上我可以说这件事现在
called chatter ping dot interval and I
叫做震颤ping点间隔，我
save that and what happens now is the
保存那个，现在发生的是
behind the scenes spring boot has
后台的 spring boot 有
regenerated the metadata they describe
重新生成他们描述的元数据
these properties our editor
这些属性是我们的编辑器
automatically picks that up and you can
自动接听，您可以
see here that it says this is deprecated
在这里看到它说这已被弃用
please use chatter ping interval instead
请改用震颤侦测间隔
and we also have a little quick fix for
我们还为
that so if i press here you can just
所以，如果我按这里，你可以
change that like that okay that's where
这样改变就可以了
i wanted to stop and hand things over to
我想停下来把东西交给
market okay great thanks Chris I will
市场还可以，非常感谢克里斯，我会
continue right exactly what Chris am
继续正确地克里斯是什么
finished but just a second don't don't
完成但只有一秒钟不要
kick off my projector cable otherwise no
踢开我的投影机电缆，否则不
one would see anything anymore yeah will
一个人会看到任何东西了，是的
do will do in a second okay let's switch
马上就会做，让我们切换
now you yeah Here I am great so what
现在你是的我在这里很棒
what I'm going to show you here is
我要在这里告诉你的是
additional features for the for the boot
用于启动的其他功能
dashboards that we implemented and to
我们实施的仪表板
make your life easier especially when
使您的生活更轻松，尤其是当
you work with cloud foundry so what I
您与Cloud Foundry合作，所以我
what I have here is the dashboard and i
我在这里的是仪表板，我
added a cloud foundry target to it so i
向它添加了一个云铸造目标，所以我
can use my Cloud Foundry stuff in the
可以在
same way as I use my local apps in my
与我在本地使用本地应用程序的方式相同
workspace I don't know if you have seen
我不知道你是否看过工作区
that before that that's kind of an old
在那之前那有点旧
feature we added some some I think some
功能我们添加了一些我认为一些
good stuff to it the first thing is I
好东西，第一件事是我
can added a bunch of them in the boot
可以在引导中添加一堆
dashboard I can now connect to them and
仪表板我现在可以连接到它们
disconnect so they are not connected at
断开连接，以便它们不连接在
startup anymore so if you if you wear
重新启动，所以如果你穿的话
may be annoyed using the old version and
使用旧版本可能会感到恼火，
have 20 20 targets and connecting
有20 20个目标并连接
everything in started up all the time
一切都一直在启动
and trying to connect everything that's
并尝试连接所有
not no longer the case you can quickly
不再如此，您可以快速
disconnect and connect to it and it
断开并连接到它和它
keeps the stage show stuff up so that's
保持舞台表演的东西，所以
great oh and I have a bunch of stuff in
太好了，我里面有很多东西
my in my workspace actually a lot of lot
我在我的工作空间中实际上很多
of old demo apps so i would like to
旧的演示应用程序，所以我想
filter them but there's there's a
过滤它们，但是有一个
service i'm kind of family that i would
服务我是我会的家庭
like to use the rabbit service so what
喜欢使用兔子服务
we added is you can put you can put tags
我们添加的是您可以放标签
on those services too so when i do the
在那些服务上，所以当我做
filtering now the service doodle shows
现在过滤服务涂鸦显示
up so I can get a get a nice overview
这样我就可以获得一个很好的概述
about what I have magically I have the
关于我神奇地拥有的
same apps that Chris Wright implemented
与Chris Wright实施的应用相同
a moment ago so that's great I can work
前一阵子很棒，我可以工作
in them and i would actually deploy them
在他们里面，我实际上会部署它们
to cloud foundry and what i would like
云铸造和我想要什么
to do is I would like to start with the
我要做的是从
command bought thing and it has many
命令买东西，它有很多
fast files Cloud Foundry manifest files
快速文件Cloud Foundry清单文件
inside that we that you can usually use
我们通常可以使用的内部
to deploy apps to Cloud Foundry like you
像您一样将应用程序部署到Cloud Foundry
put the cloud foundry specific
专门针对云代工厂
configuration in to manifest file and we
配置到清单文件中，我们
implemented nice editors for that so and
为此实现了不错的编辑器
I have in this case 2114 prod so one
在这种情况下，我有2114个针，所以一个
kind of a production environment maybe
一种生产环境
and one for my usual environment and my
和我平常的环境和我的
test environment so that's nice you can
测试环境，这样很好
open up an editor and I don't know if
打开一个编辑器，我不知道是否
you have worked with many fest files
您已经处理了许多节庆文件
before I did and I usually I can't
在我这样做之前，我通常不能
remember what I have to put in there and
记住我必须放在里面的东西
I have to look up and finally
我必须抬头终于
documentation and things like that and
文档和类似的东西，以及
but that's no longer the case because
但这不再是因为
our editor knows countenance is knows
我们的编辑知道面子就是
what belongs to Cloud Foundry manifest
什么属于Cloud Foundry清单
files so that's great I can see what
文件，所以太好了，我可以看到
properties are in there for a class
属性在那里有一堂课
family manifest file and not not only
家庭清单文件，不仅是
that I can also see documentation about
我也可以看到有关的文档
what is this property about so what I
这个财产是关于什么的
would like to do is I would like to
想做的就是我想
specify the memory settings for this
为此指定内存设置
application which I do okay put some
我做的应用程序可以放一些
memory in there get some countenance is
那里的记忆有些表情
saying oh yeah let's get a gig even a
说哦，是的，让我们一起演出
built pack let's specify build pack Java
构建包让我们指定构建包Java
bill peg and I'm done so that's great
比尔钉，我已经做好了，那太好了
gives you a lot of help for quickly
为您提供快速帮助
editing
编辑
files for cloud foundry applications so
云铸造应用程序的文件，因此
this the I this saves a lot of time for
这我节省了很多时间
me not looking at the dock anymore and
我不再看着码头了
so I can quickly do that so when I go
所以我可以很快做到
ahead and deploy my app to cloud foundry
提前将我的应用程序部署到Cloud Foundry
now using the boot dashboard just drag
现在使用启动仪表板只需拖动
and drop it asked me which manifest file
并问我哪个清单文件
to use actually what configuration
实际使用什么配置
should i use because i have multiple
我应该使用，因为我有多个
ones maybe i would like to use a totally
也许我想完全使用
different one so i get a nice dialogue
不同的，所以我得到了很好的对话
where i can select the right manifest
在这里我可以选择正确的清单
file get a nice a nice preview in this
文件在此获得不错的预览
case it shows me okay this is a preview
告诉我好吧，这是一个预览
thing I could even edit it here which I
我什至可以在这里编辑它
will not do now and go ahead with this
现在不会做，继续进行
one so that deploys the app to cloud
这样就可以将应用程序部署到云中
foundry done right it's not really done
铸造厂做对了，实际上还没有完成
because we have to wait for cloud
因为我们必须等待云
foundry to get everything uploaded and
代工来上传所有内容，
created the container and starting the
创建了容器并启动了
AB and things like that but I can also
AB和类似的东西，但我也可以
see the the lock output here nicely from
从这里很好地看到锁输出
the application so that is that's great
该应用程序，那就是太好了
it's not the only thing i would like to
这不是我唯一想做的
deploy i would also like to deploy the
部署我也想部署
banner service which is not yet on my
我尚未使用的横幅广告服务
Cloud Foundry instance and the banner
Cloud Foundry实例和横幅
service does not have any manifest file
服务没有任何清单文件
in there so I haven't specified any
在那儿，所以我没有指定
configuration so what the nice
配置怎么样
deployment dialogue does for me is it
部署对话对我有用吗
allows me to pick a different file from
允许我从中选择其他文件
somewhere in my workspace or it allows
在我工作区中的某个地方，或者它允许
me to just type in my configuration that
我只输入我的配置
I would like to use when deployed
我想在部署时使用
there's app so in this case it thought I
有应用程序，所以在这种情况下，它以为我
might use these configurations these
可能会使用这些配置
options and I can go ahead and just type
选项，我可以继续输入
in the stuff that I would like to use in
在我想用的东西
this case all the memory setting that's
这种情况下所有的内存设置
okay I don't need a bill peg don't need
好吧，我不需要结帐。
a domain here and I get all the nice
一个域在这里，我得到所有的好
features that i am familiar with with
我熟悉的功能
editing manifest files right in here too
也在这里编辑清单文件
with i think is great because for
我认为很棒，因为
example when i type in abcdefg i get an
例如，当我输入abcdefg时，我得到一个
arrow and tells me no no that's not
箭头告诉我不，不，不是
that's not a good memory thing forget
那不是好记忆的事情
countenance is I get countenance if I
容貌是我能得到容貌
try condenses get content assist and so
尝试压缩获得内容帮助，因此
on so that's I think that's that's great
所以我认为那很棒
okay so let's deploy
好吧，让我们部署
that too so both apps are being deployed
这样也可以部署两个应用程序
to cloud foundry at the moment let's see
现在到云铸造厂，让我们看看
how far they are oh it's still
他们有多远哦，仍然
downloading stuff so that's good okay so
下载东西，这样很好
let's wait for them a moment while
让我们等一下
they're being deployed to Cloud Foundry
他们被部署到Cloud Foundry
oh they the command pod is already there
哦，他们的指挥舱已经在那里
so that's that's good let's open up open
所以那就好，让我们打开
up the application and see what's going
应用程序，看看发生了什么
on there so I can just double-click the
在那儿，我可以双击
old picture of the dashboard you can
仪表板的旧图片可以
just double-click and you jump to the
只需双击，您就会跳到
default URL of the app that works for
适用于的应用程序的默认URL
local apps but it also works for apps on
本地应用程序，但也适用于
Cloud Foundry so I quickly can see
Cloud Foundry，所以我很快就能看到
what's going on on Cloud Foundry I see
我看到的Cloud Foundry发生了什么
the ping is going on and let me let me
ping正在进行，让我让我
go back here and see what's going on
回到这里，看看发生了什么
there let's see deploying that one
我们来看一下部署那个
that's okay some more stuff is going on
没关系，还有更多的事情正在进行
here some other stuff is going on here
这里还有其他的东西
okay and I think oh I think I forgot
好吧，我想哦，我想我忘了
something because I think when i was
因为我想我当时
editing the manifest file i think i
我认为我正在编辑清单文件
forgot to put in put in the service
忘了投入服务
because i would like to bind this to a
因为我想将此绑定到
service on cloud foundry which i would
我会在Cloud Foundry上提供服务
like to do now using the web console so
现在想使用网络控制台进行操作
i can quickly jump to that say open up
我可以快速跳到那说开
the web console of cloud of my cloud
我的云的云控制台
foundry instance login let's do that
铸造实例登录，让我们这样做
it's a cheddar command bought yeah
是切达命令买的
that's I think the right one and I go
那是我认为正确的选择
ahead and i bind the service my rabbit
提前，我将服务绑定到我的兔子
service let's bind that service okay I'm
服务，让我们绑定该服务好吧，我是
done that's good we can quickly restart
这样做很好，我们可以快速重新启动
the app here on my dashboard assuming
该应用程序在我的仪表板上假设
maybe I've changed some stuff locally to
也许我已经在本地更改了一些东西
or some stuff changed and in this case
或某些东西改变了，在这种情况下
it would be quite dangerous if the boot
如果启动会很危险
dashboard would just deploy the app as
仪表板会将应用程序部署为
it is again and restarted again on Cloud
它再次并在云上再次重新启动
Foundry because it would use them
铸造，因为它将使用它们
if I that I have used again and all the
如果我再次使用了所有
stuff would be lost that I change on the
我会改变的东西会丢失
cloud foundry site but luckily the
云铸造站点，但幸运的是
dashboard is smart enough to check that
仪表板足够智能，可以检查
for you so whenever you went ahead and
为了您，所以无论何时您继续前进，
change something on Claire foundry and
更改克莱尔铸造厂的某些产品并
you redeploy the app or restart the app
您重新部署应用程序或重新启动应用程序
it checks for changes for differences
它检查是否有差异
and you get a nice dip view here saying
你会在这里看到不错的倾角
hey on Cloud Foundry there is a service
嘿，Cloud Foundry上有一项服务
being bound in between locally you still
被当地人束缚着
have your manifest file not containing
您的清单文件不包含
anything what would you like to do I
任何你想做什么我
will not go ahead and just silently I
不会继续前进，只是默默地我
will write everything that you changed
将写下您更改的所有内容
it tells you and I can say okay forget
它告诉你，我可以说好吧，算了
about forget about the manifest file and
关于忘记清单文件和
don't don't associate that anymore with
不要再将其与
it or use the manifest file as it as it
或按原样使用清单文件
is because the stuff that I changed on
是因为我改变的东西
Cloud Foundry was crap or I can just go
Cloud Foundry很烂，或者我可以去
ahead and say hey merge the changes on
向前说，嘿，合并更改
Cloud Foundry to my manifest file and
Cloud Foundry到我的清单文件和
continue to use the manifest file which
继续使用清单文件
i think is great in the easy way I'm to
我认为以简单的方式很棒
keep both sides in sync and that they do
使双方保持同步，并且他们做到了
not lose anything by accident which i
我不会偶然丢失任何东西
think is great and it doesn't only work
认为很棒，这不仅有效
for services whatever you change on the
无论您更改什么服务
cloud foundry site is being reflected
云代工网站正在体现
and being reflected back to the manifest
并反映回清单
file in your local in your local
在您本地的文件中
workspace if you want to so that's great
工作空间，如果您想要的话，那很棒
going to be restarted okay so that's
将要重新启动好吧，那是
that's cool but by looking at this at
这很酷，但是通过查看
this application it's too slow right
这个应用程序太慢了吧
it's boring and print out something
很无聊，打印出一些东西
every every two seconds or whatever so
每两秒或每秒钟
we--it's bring one right we're more
我们-这带来了一种权利，我们更加
dynamic we do more stuff in less time we
动态的，我们用更少的时间做更多的事情
deploy more stuff and less time so let's
部署更多的东西和更少的时间，所以让我们
change something luckily this this ping
幸运的是，此ping更改了一些内容
bot has dev tools on it the same stuff
机器人在其上具有开发工具
that Chris showed for local apps and we
克里斯为本地应用展示的
can do the same for apps on cloud
可以对云上的应用程序执行相同的操作
foundry which is great so I just need to
铸造很棒，所以我只需要
connect a local client to this
将本地客户端连接到此
application running on Cloud Foundry
在Cloud Foundry上运行的应用程序
with deft
灵巧
tools so they connect to that so in this
工具，以便他们可以连接到这个
case now that I kind of connected my dev
现在我连接了我的开发人员
tools to the application on flat foundry
平面铸造应用程序所需的工具
I can go ahead and change my appt
我可以继续更改我的appt
locally and all the changes that I do to
在本地以及我所做的所有更改
my project locally in my workspace are
我在工作区本地的项目是
automatically being reflected on Cloud
自动反映在云端
Foundry and the efforts being restarted
代工和重新开始的努力
so what I would like to do is now I go
所以我现在想去
to the ping bought app where is it it's
到ping购买的应用程序，它在哪里
here pinball app there's my
这是弹球应用程序
configuration and let's let's change
配置，让我们进行更改
this to a shorter shorter time ok so I
这可以缩短时间，所以我
save that I go back to to the thing as
除非我回到那件事
being uploaded it's kind of the devtools
被上传是一种devtools
restart stuff under the hood and boom
重新启动引擎盖下的东西
there it is right it's changed the AB on
那里是对的，它改变了AB
Cloud Foundry so that makes your app
Cloud Foundry，使您的应用程序
development while pushing it at the same
同时推动发展
time to Cloud Foundry working with apps
是时候使用Cloud Foundry处理应用程序了
on Cloud Foundry from your IDE a lot
在您的IDE上大量使用Cloud Foundry
easier right you do not have to report
更轻松的权利，您不必报告
restart everything over the wire over
重新启动所有内容
and over again you can just quickly make
再来一次，您可以快速制作
changes but take care right this is not
变化，但要注意，这不是
for production usage yeah and you know
用于生产，是的，你知道
all the changes you make silently under
您默默进行的所有更改
the hood on your container well we wiped
您擦拭容器上的引擎盖好了
out by cloud foundry from time to time
有时会被云铸造厂淘汰
and kind of if it figures out how you
如果它弄清楚了你如何
change something under the hood these
改变这些东西
kind of snowflakes is not allowed and so
那种雪花是不允许的，所以
it will restart the container for you
它将为您重新启动容器
but while doing these kind of
但是在做这些
development tasks that's that's really
真正的开发任务
nice and really handy really cool and
很好，很方便，很酷，
it's directly supported from usps so
它直接由usps支持，因此
that's that's nice ok let me stop that
那很好，让我停止
again from time to time and you don't
时不时地你不会
really know what where the problem is so
真的知道问题出在哪里
you first have to find out what is the
您首先必须找出什么是
problem so let's try to see if my banner
问题，让我们尝试看看我的横幅广告
service is is working now oh wow yeah
服务正在运作中喔喔耶
it's a printing out spring one platform
这是一个春季印刷的平台
2016 that's great but maybe something is
2016年很棒，但也许有些
not working inside of this service what
无法在此服务内工作
should I do now
我现在应该做
maybe it's only not working when I'm on
也许只有当我在
foundry maybe it's a problem in general
铸造也许是一个普遍的问题
and the service but maybe I don't want
和服务，但也许我不想
to kick off everything locally as Chris
像克里斯一样在当地开始一切
did I would like to reuse the
我想重用
application that is already running all
已经运行了所有的应用程序
the stuff that are running on my cloud
我的云上运行的东西
because that's that's what my cloud is
因为那就是我的云
for right I can put everything on there
我可以把所有东西放在那里
on my 20 100 1000 come back to the
在我的20100 1000上
question second 1000m microservices
质疑第二个1000m微服务
they're all running on Cloud Foundry but
它们都在Cloud Foundry上运行，但是
I would like to take a look at one
我想看一个
specific part that might contain a buck
可能包含降压的特定部分
in this case maybe it's my banner
在这种情况下，也许是我的旗帜
service so what I can do now and then I
服务，所以我现在可以做些什么
could occur also do it in the previous
可能也会发生
version but I'm so excited about that I
版本，但我对此感到非常兴奋
have to show you that again is you can
必须告诉你，再次是你可以
start up the banner service locally and
在本地启动横幅广告服务，
expose that to Cloud Foundry to the
将其暴露给Cloud Foundry
service registry on Cloud Foundry so I i
Cloud Foundry上的服务注册表，所以我
start the banner service locally and i
在本地启动横幅广告服务
select the service registry on Cloud
选择云上的服务注册表
Foundry that this service should
代工，该服务应
register itself to and it will do that
注册自己，它将这样做
so it will never forget about the break
所以它永远不会忘记休息
point it will start up the service
点它将启动服务
locally on my machine right step one
本地在我的机器上正确的第一步
step two it will open up a tunnel to the
第二步，它将打开通往
outside world so that someone from
外面的世界，以便某人从
outside can use the service that is
外部可以使用的服务是
running on my local machine and it's a
在我的本地计算机上运行
third step it will register my locally
第三步它将在本地注册我
running service with the remote eureka
远程尤里卡运行服务
on Cloud Foundry as a result whenever
结果是在Cloud Foundry上
this service on Cloud Foundry is being
Cloud Foundry上的此服务正在
called by all the other components on
由所有其他组件调用
Cloud Foundry my whole system that's
Cloud Foundry我的整个系统
running there it's been routed to my
在那儿跑，它已经路由到我的
local service on my machine so I can
我机器上的本地服务，这样我就可以
debug that so i can go ahead to my
调试，以便我可以继续进行
banner service and say hey let's put a
横幅广告服务，说嘿，让我们
breakpoint in here oh there is a
断点在这里哦，有一个
breakpoint so that's great so let's try
断点，这很好，让我们尝试
let's try and see what happens when I
让我们尝试看看当我发生什么
kick
踢
of the banner again Wow goes to my local
的旗帜又来了哇
machine I can debug the service locally
机器，我可以在本地调试服务
on my machine even though the rest of my
在我的机器上，即使我的其余部分
system is fully running on Cloud Foundry
系统在Cloud Foundry上完全运行
so I haven't I don't have to start
所以我没有我不必开始
everything locally and do everything
一切都在本地做
locally on my machine and then kicked
在我的机器上本地然后踢
over a rabid and kick off all the other
狂暴地踢开所有其他
Microsoft's that are running maybe from
正在运行的Microsoft可能来自
my from my for my teammates maybe from
我从我为我的队友，也许从
other teams and so on i can just debug
其他团队等等，我可以调试
stuff locally on my machine which i
我的机器上本地的东西
think is great so when I when I would it
认为很棒，所以当我愿意的时候
continue it would continue with the flow
继续，它将继续流动
and all the rest and cloud foundry all
所有其余的和云铸造厂
the other services would just continue
其他服务将继续
to work with i think is a great step
与我合作是迈出的重要一步
forward when you work in this micro
在这个微型电脑上工作时前进
service cloud native world where your
服务云原生世界，您的
abdul not longer consists out of one big
阿卜杜勒不再由一个大的组成
thing that you can start up locally it
你可以在本地启动的东西
contains out of maybe hundreds or
包含数百或
thousands of micro services running on
数以千计的微服务正在运行
Cloud Foundry so that's I think a very
Cloud Foundry，所以我认为
nice feature in the boot dashboard to
引导仪表板中的好功能
allow you to do more stuff okay there
允许你在那里做更多的事情
was a kind of a quick demo of some some
是一些一些的快速演示
nice new things that we that we put in
我们投入的美好的新事物
and some ideas and some some some
还有一些想法，还有一些
features that we put in to make you love
我们投入让您爱的功能
you basically your life easier right you
你基本上你的生活更轻松吧
would like to make your life easier
希望让您的生活更轻松
whenever you have something in your mind
每当你有什么想法
we think hey this annoys me would be
我们认为嘿，这会让我很烦
great if you could do if could help me
如果可以的话可以帮助我，很好
with XYZ let us know you're very open to
XYZ让我们知道您很愿意接受
that we would really love to hear from
我们非常希望听到
you what is missing maybe or hey this
你可能缺少什么或嘿
stuff from the boot dashboard that's
引导仪表板中的
really annoying because i have to do
真的很烦，因为我必须做
these 10 clicks and it doesn't work all
这10次点击无法全部正常
the time let us know okay what you've
时间让我们知道好吗
seen wizards for quickly getting started
见过快速入门的向导
with spring bood easily managing
弹簧易于管理
dependencies adding additional spring
依赖添加了额外的spring
boot dependencies additional spring boot
启动依赖项附加的Spring Boot
starters is very easy with the edit
入门非常容易，编辑
starters thing we put in a lot of code
首先，我们投入了很多代码
new code templates tiny little code
新的代码模板小小的代码
templates that make your typing life
模板，让您打字生活
easier and quicker we showed you the
更方便快捷地向您展示了
advanced support for editing
先进的编辑支持
d files and llamo files config files for
d个文件和llamo文件的配置文件
spring boot and I think that's really
spring boot ，我认为那是真的
awesome I really love that and I can I
很棒，我真的很喜欢，我可以
can very easily just type something in
可以很容易地输入
and with these smart content search
并借助这些智能内容搜索
thing magically shows up the right
事物神奇地显示正确
property files and shows me some
属性文件，并向我展示了一些
documentation I think is really cool the
我认为文档确实很棒
boot dashboard kind of establishes
启动仪表盘的种类
itself nowadays there's some kind of a
如今，它本身具有某种
micro service development center you can
可以的微服务开发中心
easily start and stop your boobs they're
轻松启动和停止它们的胸部
dealing with many boobs filter apps
处理许多胸部过滤器应用程序
that's cool the glue I showed you the
我给你看的胶水太酷了
cloud foundry integration some debugging
云铸造集成一些调试
for that and some some ideas and some
为此，一些想法和一些
some features to really shorten the
一些功能可以真正缩短
turnaround cycles when dealing with apps
处理应用程序时的周转周期
on Cloud Foundry and many small tips and
有关Cloud Foundry和许多小技巧，以及
tricks along the way but what we up to
一路把戏，但我们要做什么
the next release cycles we showed us TS
在接下来的发行周期中，我们向我们展示了TS
swing tool suite and we released 381
摆动工具套件，我们发布了381
just yesterday so really hot of the
就在昨天，真的很热
press the next maintenance releases will
按下一个维护版本将
ship kind of in sync with in with the
船种与
next Eclipse releases so we are always
下一个Eclipse版本，所以我们总是
trying to adopt the latest eclipse
试图采用最新的日食
releases Eclipse neon came out in June
Eclipse霓虹灯发布于六月
so we adopted that neon wonder 203 take
所以我们采用了霓虹灯奇迹203
care free maintenance releases now from
现在免费维护版本
eclipse neon this time we will adopt
这次，我们将采用霓虹
them in shipshape versions kind of one
他们在船形版本的那种
or two weeks after after that and this
或之后的两个星期
dream will focus on fixing box improving
梦想将集中在改进盒子上
maybe performance improving stability
也许性能提高稳定性
adding tiny little things here and there
在这里和那里添加微小的小东西
and adopting those releases the big the
并采用那些发布大
big thing afterwards the stuff that we
大事之后，我们
start to work on now is st s4 which will
现在开始工作是st s4
be the major release its kind of may be
是主要的发行版本
previewed next year so come back to
明年预览，请回到
spring one platform next year so make
明年春季推出一个平台，使
sure you register for conference you get
确保您注册参加会议
a get a hot preview of SCS for which
获得SCS的热门预览
will kind of a major will be a major
会专业，会专业
review may
审查可能
to rework of the tooling and will change
返工的工具，将改变
dramatically under the hood adopting
显着采用
completely new architecture that makes
全新的架构使
it a lot more performant more stable and
表现更稳定，
it really does the latest architectures
它确实是最新的架构
that are kind of the kind of makes sense
这是很有意义的
if you develop IDEs nowadays the elds
如果您现在开发IDE，
tooling is still based on how eclipse
工具仍然基于日食
was built ten years ago and with a cs4
建于十年前，并带有CS4
we are kind of really moving into the
我们真的在进入
future of building IDEs and giving you
开发IDE并给您带来的未来
the latest stuff on the on the best
最好的最新的东西
architecture that is available nowadays
当今可用的架构
for building developer tooling okay with
用于构建开发人员工具
that I would like to thank you all for
我要感谢大家
attending of course we are open for
当然参加我们是开放的
questions we still have a little bit of
问题，我们还有一点
time because we got these extra ten
时间，因为我们得到了这额外的十个
minutes and now it's just extra six
分钟，现在只剩下六分钟
minutes some references so if you want
分钟一些参考，所以如果你想
to ask questions when you headed off
出发时问问题
home after the conference feel free to
发布会后回家
ask questions instead overflow we
问问题反而溢出我们
monitor that file issues download SDS of
监视文件问题，下载SDS
course if you haven't done already and
当然，如果您还没有完成，
I'm happy to answer a few questions
我很高兴回答几个问题
right now otherwise don't miss those
现在，否则不要错过那些
other talks about productivity so if
其他谈论生产力，所以如果
you're interested IntelliJ this is 1
您有兴趣IntelliJ这是1
inch LG I tips and tricks one on spring
英寸LG I春季小技巧
boot productivity hope you enjoyed the
引导生产力希望您喜欢
conference and I'd like to thank you all
会议，我要谢谢大家
thanks for coming
感谢你的到来
you
您